This is Wyatt from Castle Island, and today's episode of On the Brink was the first of a
series on StablecoinFi where we'll talk to leading players building stablecoin-focused
applications in DeFi. Today, I was joined by Kedian Sun, the founder of Level Money.
Level is the issuer of LevelUSD, a DeFi-native stablecoin backed by other major stablecoins
including USDT and USDC earning yield in low-risk DeFi lending strategies to offer a DeFi risk-free
rate. LevelUSD has over $140 million dollars in supply after just over six months in market
and continues to grow rapidly. Kedian and I discussed the adoption of incumbent stablecoins
versus newcomers, the evolution of stablecoin-based finance, and what's ahead for Level among other
topics. I hope you enjoy this episode. Matt Walsh and Nick Carter are partners at Castle
Island Ventures. All views expressed by them or the guests on this podcast are solely their
opinions and do not reflect the opinions of Castle Island Ventures. Guests and hosts may
maintain positions in the assets discussed on this podcast. You should not treat any
opinion expressed by anyone on this podcast as a specific inducement to make a particular
investment or follow a particular strategy, but only as an expression of their personal opinion.
This podcast is for informational purposes only. Brought down by bad mortgage investments,
Lehman, which has 25,000 employees, will be liquidated. The federal government loans
American International Group, AIG, $85 billion. This is a different kind of market and the Fed
is asleep. The federal government is stepping in to stabilize Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac. The
two mortgage giants that have been threatened by the housing crisis. The Bank of England has
pumped 75 billion pounds more into Britain's ailing economy with a new round of quantitative
easing. You print a couple trillion dollars and all of a sudden people start to worry. So out of
this worry, we have something called the Bitcoin. Bitcoin. Well, Kadeen, thanks for joining. Excited
to chat today. Would love to learn a little bit more about you to start, if you don't mind giving
a personal background and telling us a little bit about Level. Yeah, of course. First of all,
you're excited to be here. Thanks for having me. A little bit about myself. So I'm Kadeen.
I'm originally from New Zealand and came to the US for college. My background is in finance. I
studied finance at Wharton, did investment banking after graduation at an investment bank called
Lazard here in New York for a few years. And then I worked in FinTech at a company called Brex for a
few years. And so, yeah, I guess my entire career has been kind of seeing different ways of like
money moving around essentially. I first got involved in crypto. I think it was my senior
year of college. Basically, I think a very classic story a friend told me about ETH.
I just went ahead and bought a bag, had no clue how the tech worked, what this meant for the
world in the future. But I think that was sort of like my entry point into crypto and how I
continued to stay sort of in the loop with crypto while I was working in more traditional industries
and banking and FinTech. And then while I was at Brex NSF, that was when I linked up with my
co-founder who was working as an engineer at Flexport there. That was kind of like how we just
started jamming and got into crypto full-time from there. So, yeah, that's kind of just a
little bit about myself. Do you want me to get started on talking about like how we got started
with Level? Yeah, talk about Level and how you guys got started. Cool. Yeah, so I guess we weren't
always Level. I mean, we started in the stablecoin space in March of 2023 and it was a different name
back then. I guess like the story of how we actually got into stablecoins, like I said,
it was March of 2023. If you remember, this was a big month for stablecoins and for crypto
because that was when USDC de-pegged as a result of like the SVB collapse. And so I think that
news got like our attention. Yeah, because previously we actually weren't, well, everyone's
obviously heard of stablecoins, probably had used them on Coinbase or other exchanges, but it wasn't
something that I actually really looked into. I just sort of like trusted that these stablecoins
were pegged to a dollar. That they worked? You just trusted that they worked? Yeah, exactly. Which
obviously March 2023 kind of destroyed that view, at least temporarily. And so I would say that
despite that being probably the lowest sentiment ever in stablecoins, we sort of were able to build
up a lot of conviction at that point. Thought this was sort of like the future of crypto and
even like the future of finance and just started building in the space. I mean, even at that point,
I think people were still, like other than that event, people were starting to pay a lot more
attention to stablecoins. But I think it's especially being in the last year where it's
just become consensus. And, you know, we're just seeing so much stablecoin activity, I think,
since 2024. And then I think the other moment for me, this was a little bit more personally,
is like, I think after looking into that, I also just happened to make my first actual cross border
stablecoin transaction during around that time. And I know this sounds almost silly that there
was this first time, but I think when we live in sort of developed countries at the US or in the
West, the banking system is generally not too bad. So you don't actually need to use stablecoins
that much, especially for domestic use cases. But in this case was me trying to send some money to
a friend in Australia, we actually tried to do it through like the traditional banking system first.
And, you know, it's just like a very classic story of like, and this is from the US to Australia,
it's like nothing crazy, right? It took days before it got bounced, right? And then it's like,
the next thing tried was like USDC. And it literally just arrived in seconds. It's like
that kind of magic moment for me. I think that was also what gave me even more conviction than
stablecoins. But going back to level, we've actually tried a few different stablecoin models.
The first version was essentially a feedback stablecoin that shared the treasury yield with
distribution partners. So this is actually quite similar to what Agora is trying to do now.
We ran into a couple of challenges building this. The first was actually building a feedback stablecoin
takes a lot of time, because especially at that point, you had to work with partner banks or
custodians, treasury providers. And it's like, whenever you have to work with a centralized
party, especially like a regulated one, it's just like a really slow process.
And even incumbents, right? Even incumbents who've been around and have a degree of capture
with those players. Yeah, exactly. So it probably took us like six months to even get set up. And
to be honest, like the custody model wasn't even good. We sort of like strung together custodians
and treasury providers. And actually, I think a lot of the feedback we got from the legitimate
players in the space was like, we can't trust this thing. But yeah, I think we tried to go to
market with this model by offering to pay people the treasury yield, and they sort of found increased
adoption for us. I think we initially mostly focused on DeFi. And in crypto, people don't
really care about 5% yields and DeFi, right? So that wasn't very successful. And then institutions,
I think it was just like, obviously, also very hard to break into. And I think the custody model
was a bit of a question. And so basically found that that didn't work. And then we started trying
to build almost like an Athena competitor, actually had a similar issue of it took so much
time to onboard with exchanges and custodians. And then I think ultimately, we actually just
personally didn't feel like this was the stable coin or synthetic dollar model that we sort of
resonated with and what we were in terms of what we were trying to build long term. But yeah,
regardless, I think both those things taught us a lot about building stable coins, and at least
trying to go to market with them. And then last August, we started building Level in its current
form. And so this is a fully level, like level USD is fully built on chain. So actually, first
thing that was nice is that we could build it really quickly. We didn't need to rely on any
third parties to start building. We could just build on Ethereum, use USDC, USDT. We were building
on our way like lending protocols more generally. And so we were able to get it together quite
quickly. And yeah, what we ended up with was actually like a very simple stable point,
like level USD is fully backed by USDC and USDT. Obviously, the two largest and most trusted stable
feedback stable coins in the space right now. And then what we do is generate yield on like the
USDC and USDT reserves. Specifically, we focus on really low risk sources of yield. And this for us
was like lending protocols, you know, people talk about RBA as essentially like the crypto risk free
rate. And so we just park all of our capital there right now, we will be expanding to other
blue chip lending protocols. So specifically, more for prime vaults is coming up in the next few
weeks. But yeah, the idea here is like, you know, a very low risk source of yield that's also very
liquid to back like level USD. And then, you know, the protocol accumulates this yield and we pass it
back to the users through like a pretty standard 4626 staking mechanism. So that's essentially
like the journey of us building level and then kind of a quick summary of how it actually works.
And to break that down and almost read it back so that everyone has a sense,
you guys backing level USD, you have USDT and USDC that is deposited in these relatively safe
strategies on Aave and soon to be Morpho as well. So on top of that level USD, that's then also an
asset that can be used in longer tail pools within DeFi and for DeFi use cases.
Yeah, exactly. I think a quick point is that technically after we deploy the assets,
level USD is backed by the lending protocol receipt token. So it's like the A tokens,
the Morpho Vault tokens, eventually, etc. And then yeah, correct. So level USD itself is like this
commissionless asset. People can use it however they want really. What we have done is integrated
into other leading DeFi protocols like Pendle, Morpho for collateral, etc. And so yeah, people
can go ahead and use level as well as S level USD, which is the yield bearing counterpart,
kind of like wherever they want or wherever it is integrated.
Yep, very cool. I'm curious for your view because you guys clearly spent some time in
the discovery space when it comes to building in stablecoins. In your view, why another stablecoin
issuer and why another stablecoin when we have USDC, we have USDC. And on top of that,
how did you land on issuing a stablecoin or building a stablecoin primitive as opposed to say
building an application around an existing large stablecoin?
I think that's a really good question. I think the first thing is actually, I know there's a
lot of ways to sort of segment stablecoins, but at least in this context, I think there's like
stablecoins that are used or that are, I think, more designed to be used for like reward payments.
And then there are stablecoins that are actually more like yield assets. And I actually personally
think it's a bit of a misnomer to call these stablecoins yield bearing stablecoins or like
stablecoins generally. And just because I think there's not like any stablecoins folder sort of
like as an industry, we've adopted these terms. But if you look at the yield bearing version of
stablecoins, including our own, that's not a stablecoin because it's not pegged to a dollar.
It's increasing in value as it accumulates yield or it's like rebasing, right? It's just actually
not a stablecoin. And so I think I'll start with that category of like why we need more of these.
And I think the answer is basically that it's like at the end of the day, these are yield
assets that you can think compared to the fixed income market in traditional finance.
Obviously, it's fixed income. By definition, the income is supposed to be fixed. In crypto,
it's usually not fixed. But the idea is that the principle stays relatively pegged to the dollar
and you can earn yield on top. And so in that case, there's a market for like thousands of these.
If we look at Tradfied, like the fixed income market is actually bigger than the equities
market. And there's literally thousands or tens of thousands of options out there. And so I think
that's where like what we commonly call yield bearing stablecoins. So I think more accurately,
like yield tokens kind of comes in. And then in terms of kind of these more like payment stablecoins,
the root of your question is basically probably implying that we don't need that many of them
because there's sort of network effects around stablecoins. And I think that probably is the
future state. There might not be too many of them. But that being said, I think the reason that there
are a lot of them popping up now and the reason that we actually need a lot of them is actually
good for like the stablecoin industry. Because I have a pretty strong belief and we see this in
most industries. The winners of like the early stages of a new industry or like the winners now
are not necessarily the winners of the future. And you sort of need a lot of competition to
essentially increase like the service area of innovation. And so I think this is why it's
actually a good thing for a lot of new stablecoins to be built right now. Everyone's trying to be
innovative in some way. And this actually pushes forward the industry. And sure, maybe Tether will
continue to be the winner even for a very long time, especially if they can continue being
innovative. But I think there's also a very good chance that one of these new stablecoins will
become like the Tether of tomorrow. And I think that's my view on like the number of stablecoins
that are popping up, even though I think people are starting to complain about them. To answer
your question about like why we decided to build like pick up your stablecoin issuer, as opposed
to building something on top of existing stablecoins. Especially when we first started,
the stablecoin industry was much less sophisticated. It was essentially just like an industry of like
issuers. And there was a lot of value to being an issuer, or at least like the perceived value was
like very high. And so I think that's where we started. But I do agree with you. And this is sort
of part of like our longer term goals is that it's actually very important to build applications
around stablecoins. And so there's two options here. You can build on top of other stablecoins,
or stablecoins can build applications or like facilitate the building of applications on top
of themselves. And so I think we started by being an issuer. And I think we've at least
have some good signs of early traction as an issuer. But yeah, the long term goal is actually
to try to like answer the question about how do we actually increase the usage of our stablecoin
or stablecoins more generally. I want to double click because I think you made one really
interesting point there in particular, which is we might have sort of a narrow reality for
traditional payments, USD stablecoins, maybe what people think of first when they think of
stablecoins, which is the USDT and USDC. And then I would hope as I think you do that we have this
longer tail, things that we call stablecoins functionally today, but maybe it's a real estate
backed asset that has some sort of dollar denominated value, but appreciates in value,
hopefully, maybe it's a defi risk free rate along the lines of what you guys are doing. But
there's longer tail of things which should have stable issue value that hopefully appreciates.
The point I wanted to ask is, do you think that we get to a point where the true stablecoins,
so called the USDTs and USDCs are used for payments? Or do you think we get to a world where
these hopefully continually value accretive assets that are similar to stablecoins, but
pegged or denominated in something that should appreciate in value, do those become used as
payments? And then we can get to a world where we're settling transactions and paying for things
in something other than what is still a fiat rooted asset. Yeah, good question. Personally,
I believe we don't see that. And the reason was, I think people have certain expectations of like
what they use as money. And I think having an asset that's backed by longer tail stuff, I think
in theory, it's that you can use that as a method of payment. And yeah, I think with crypto or
blockchains, it does make that theoretically easier. But I don't think that's going to be widely
accepted. So if you go to a merchant, they just want to know that it's a dollar. The merchant is
going to understand the hundred different types of these dollar pegged assets that are backed by
long tail assets. And so that's something that's very feasible. And then the other thing is just
related to risk. Just because something is pegged to the dollar and has been historically, doesn't
actually mean that it is very safe and doesn't mean that it won't depeg in the future. And I
think we saw this with the stablecoin that was backed by real estate. And because real estate
is a liquid, the stablecoin depegged by like 50%, I think it was called USR or something like that.
This happened, I think, end of 2023 or sometime in 2024. And so yeah, that's sort of why I don't
really believe that anything that's not truly a liquid stablecoin that's backed by safe assets
can actually be used as a form of money or payment. To your point, even if vendors
don't want to accept those longer tail stablecoin assets, that's why I'm personally very excited
about some of the pay with crypto and credit card functionalities that are being built because
it's much easier. Let's say I own tokenized Tesla stock and I want to use that as what is
functionally my credit card payment asset. I can easily swipe a card and you can go from that Tesla
asset to stable coins and the stable coins can either go to the vendor or it can convert to
dollars and that can all happen very quickly. Whereas from what I know, the functionality of
some of the traditional pay with stocks, the settlement just actually takes so long and it's
so inefficient and equity markets run on market hours and crypto markets run 24 seven. So I could
see maybe some sort of middle ground there where you can hold over asset and the stable coins,
the USDC type stable coins are used as the instantaneous transaction method.
Yeah, I think what we both said is actually true. So I agree with you that there can be
these abstraction layers that make it very easy to convert from certain assets to stable coins
that are used for payments. But I think what you describe as two separate processes, right? Like
you're using these assets as a store of value. That's what you're holding them for as a user.
But then it's like when you go to make the payment, ultimately you're selling off. And like you said,
crypto facilitates the very easy conversion of these assets, but the actual payment is still
made in like the payments. Yep, definitely. So looking at level USD in this stable coin landscape,
last time I checked, I think this was last night, there's about 140 million in supply. I don't know
if that's changed much over the last 12 hours, but where does this supply sit today? Like where
does it exist? Is it in wallets? Is it in user wallets exchanges? And how is it being used? Who's
using it? Yeah, good question. So I think since last time, we've actually grown to about 145.
So sort of consistently growing in terms of where it's used. Right now it is used mostly
for DeFi use cases as a way to generate yield. So we have part of the supply that's sitting in
curve for liquidity. A lot of people have stake level USD for S level USD in order to earn the
yield. So right now approximately one third of level USD is staked. And then with S level USD,
you can then take it and use it elsewhere. So for example, on like Pindle, it's also accepted as
collateral on some vaults and Morpho as well. And then, yeah, like I mentioned, Pindle is just
generally a huge use case for both unstaked as well as staked level USD. And then yesterday,
I don't know if you saw, but we basically did some big announcements and we're continuing to do
announcements this week about level USD and related assets being able to be used as collateral on
Morpho for borrowing. So these are like probably like the main use cases currently. And then,
yeah, in terms of who are the users, it's sort of very split between like institutions and retail.
I think, you know, with crypto being permissionless, sometimes it's hard to tell,
but we do see wallets that are transacting like that are minting and then using like
millions of dollars of level USD at a time. But then we also have people that are literally doing
like a few dollars at a time. And so just depending on where you define the line between retail and
institutions slash whales, we have like a really wide spectrum. And do you guys want level to be a
fairly permissionless asset in the sense that anyone in DeFi who wants to build a pool or wants
to integrate it in some capacity can do so? Or do you want to be selective with partners?
My thinking here is if you have folks who are going really far out on the risk curve in terms
of what their pools look like in terms of creating vaults that might be backing another asset or
stable coin, do you guys have a selection threshold? Do you want to discourage folks
you might not align with from a risk perspective or how do you vet people who would be working with
level USD? Yeah, it's permissionless so anyone can use it. And we are starting to see protocols
actually reach out to us. I think they want to like have our blessing, but we don't always
give that but then they still go ahead and create it. They're free to do whatever they want with
these assets, right? It's kind of like a very core principle of crypto and DeFi. In terms of protocols
that we do put a more active effort into integrating for now, like we are quite selective here.
And like, as you can probably tell, like we've literally just integrated with protocols that
are already very established, very trusted. And so I think this includes the yield trading
protocols like Pindle and Spectra, and then Morpho is like a big one and Morpho and other
more like blue chip lending protocols that won't accept us as collateral. And so I think it's
actually almost like pretty easy to know like who are like these kind of more leading protocols.
And that's also changing, right? You have protocols that are growing, but yeah, there's probably only
really a handful of those. And then we also, we don't actually discourage people from integrating
level USD. But you know, we do see that with protocols that are not that they're not good,
as I said, they're smaller currently and they could be like the blue chips of tomorrow.
With that in mind, the growth of level USD, how do you look at growth on Ethereum main net
versus other blockchains? It seems like you have a couple of different arenas there. There's main
net, there's Solana and other VMs, there's Monad and Barrett chain and MegaEath and some of these
newer EVM chains. And then you're also seeing a newer rise of folks who are trying to build
stablecoin specific chains. So I'm curious how you look at
where is the game to be played in your view and where are the major stablecoins going to exist
and transact? Yeah, I think right now we're just very focused on Ethereum. I think despite a lot
of complaints about Ethereum, like it is the place with the most liquidity with the most EFI activity.
And I think until we saturate like Ethereum, we probably wouldn't actively go to other
chains unless there's like a very good reason to do so from a distribution perspective.
That being said, I think eventually, especially if we want to move towards more of these like
payment or money use cases. And first of all, Ethereum's fees are also great recently, right?
So that's actually not as big of a problem as it used to be. But obviously it still is, I think,
higher than a lot of these L2s or alternative chains. And so I think in terms of like when we
do get to that stage of trying to be used more for smaller transactions and for payments, then
it probably does make sense to have level USD on those chains and kind of have those be the
settlement layers. In terms of your question about stablecoins, like purposeful stablecoin
chains, I think this is a very interesting topic. So I think at a level we actually do believe kind
of in the value proposition of these chains. The reality is that existing blockchains aren't built
for stablecoins specifically, right? They've sort of been built for like the more speculative cases
of crypto. And I think as Codex, when they announced, I actually liked their quote where
they said that right now, I think the way people are building on stablecoins is kind of like,
I think they said it's like jerry-rigging together a bunch of plumbing that wasn't built
for this purpose originally. And I actually do resonate with that. And I can go into details
around exactly why that is the case. But yeah, that being said, obviously there are already
like trillions of dollars worth of stablecoins being transacted on existing chains. So it's
not that they don't work, but I think it's actually that stablecoin solves such a big problem that
the existing chains are a good enough solution for now, even despite like where they do lack.
I think if we want to really scale this thing, we really want to scale stablecoin use cases.
I think we do think that these stablecoin chains do serve value. And specifically,
there's probably a few categories off the top of my head. The first is actually related to compliance.
And so I think the fact that public block like, you know, fully permissionless blockchains have
permissionless validators is actually a problem for adoption for like certain institutions.
Because when you make a transaction, you could be then directly paying like a validator in North
Korea, for example. And that's kind of just no go for a lot of institutions. And so I'm pretty
sure all of these chains are building permission validators, if there are no one. And then the
other two are more like UI, UX related. One is just like, it actually doesn't really make sense
to use arbitrary volatile tokens to be paying for transactions, right? That's clearly not built
for stablecoin transactions. And we do have the things abstract that away, but it's sort of like,
that's not really how it should be built from first principles. And I think the final one is
just privacy. So publicly owned blockchains, you know, it's kind of a feature and a bug where
it is fully public. But like, if you are getting your salary paid in stable coins, I'm sure you
don't prefer that to be public, right? So yeah, that's kind of like our view on all of various
chains and yes, specifically stablecoin chains. Yeah. Another argument I've heard, which I think
makes sense is that to your point earlier, most of the chains we interact with today are built for
permissionless finance and a permissionless building out of use cases. Presumably an enterprise
grade chain that's meant to settle stable coins would actually be limited in scope and functionality
in terms of certain financial use cases, in terms of asset issuance, in terms of some guardrails
that would give comfort, just more so that the users of traditional institutions wouldn't
potentially venture onto something that could be either dangerous from a security perspective or
from a high risk perspective. So we believe, and it looks to be the case that that stable coins
will continue to grow as a share of on-chain assets. And with that in mind will be a growing
piece of DeFi. How do you think DeFi evolves around that stable coin growth and as stable
coins constitute a wider share of on-chain assets and of DeFi? Yeah, I mean, I think DeFi is like
built to support both stable as well as non-stable activity. And so we might have DeFi protocols that
are specifically built to make stable coins or yield bearing stable coins more useful.
But I think generally speaking, I do believe that's probably what we're going to evolve into.
And this is basically just like, we're going to start seeing relatively less speculative activity
in DeFi and then have more of these stable coin or dollar pegged type of assets.
And this sort of goes back to what I was saying earlier, if we look at traditional finance,
like the fixed income market is bigger than the equities market. And I think right now,
if you compare the speculative side of crypto to equities and then the stable coin side to
fixed income, well, if anything, actually, I think stable coins is already almost like on par now.
And so I think we will see more of that. And I think that's going to be like the longer term
trend because at the end of the day, pure speculation, it's always going to be around.
That's why casinos exist too. But at the end of the day, casinos are a much smaller market than
like actually a functional finance. Yep, makes sense. In your view, is there also a white space
for stable coins pegged to other fiat currencies? That's been another topic people have been talking
about recently. Or do you think this stays mostly dollarized? No, I think absolutely. I mean,
I think in DeFi, I think US dollar stable coins will dominate just because it's become kind of
like, I mean, even in Tradify, the US dollar is the global reserve currency. And then in DeFi,
when it's even more borderless, it's even more so. Yeah, so DeFi use cases, I still do think US dollar
stable coins will dominate. And then for like real world use cases, like the reality is most places
outside the US, a lot of them don't accept US dollars, even though I guess people are starting
to accept them more. And so for I think to increase adoption in those jurisdictions, it's like
basically every currency, I think will need their own stable coin. And there's actually a lot of
room to grow for them. And then that being said, it's kind of like if you do have stable coins
other currencies, and they're on chain, then there is like this market for I think, games and like
trading around different currencies, stable coins. So yeah, so I think it will grow a lot. We're not
going to see a future where we only have US dollar stable coins being 99% of the market,
especially as we develop more real world use cases. Got it. No, it's very helpful. And is the core
product level USD? Is that going to be the primary focus for the time being? Are you guys going to
look into these other sorts of stable coin primitives or, or what's on your mind going forward?
Yeah, good question. We sort of think about growth in two phases for new stable coins is always the
first part, which is scaling and building up like credibility and essentially a brand as a stable
coin. So I think during this phase, we're going to essentially focus on what we're doing now,
which is like this more defi native stable coin built on lending protocols,
because like continue to consistently offer more attractive risk return profile. So this includes
high yield, continue our low risk strategies, and then also just really increase like the utility
and capital efficiency through just like integrating with a lot of defi protocols.
Our view is actually that new stable coins actually have to expand beyond just being a
stable coin issuer. I think there's a lot of different ways to do this, but I think I'm
stealing a quote probably from an MZero interview. I think one of the founders or someone there was
saying that the stable coins now are kind of like the Blackberries or like the Nokia's in the early
days of phones. And then as we've seen, obviously like pure phone makers, they lost, right? And I
think that's kind of like potentially how to think about stable coins. Now it's like, if you're just
a stable coin issuer, that means you're the equivalent of just being like a phone manufacturer.
And we've obviously seen like, you know, Apple's the most successful phone of all time. And the
reason for that is because they were building value add like it's products on top of that,
including like the App Store and a bunch of other things. And so I think especially for new stable
coins, like the low hanging fruit of partnering with exchanges or like trying to basically get
distribution, purely partnering up or paying for distribution is probably not going to be enough.
And so we do believe that stable coins do need to build value add services themselves to increase
their distribution. Like I said, there's a lot of different ways you can approach this. And this is
something that we're thinking a lot about, not going to reveal I think too much here, but yeah,
that's the idea is that we will be moving into building products that are going to increase
like the utility as well as the use case and distribution of our core primitives, which is
level USD. Very cool. And broadly speaking, I wanted to ask in closing here, what are you
excited about and what keeps you up at night? In general, I'm actually just very excited about
crypto, which is probably right now a little bit contrarian because you obviously see so much doom
with crypto, but I guess that is more related to like the speculative side. And if anything,
like when it's a bear market and I keep stealing people's calls, I think it was like Sam from
Frax that said this, a bear market for crypto or like for the markets is actually a bull market
for stable coins. And so yeah, kind of despite the rest of the market and you know, obviously
want everyone to stay safe, not lose their money, but it's kind of like actually a really good time
for stable coins to be building. And I think we're seeing so many stable coin issuers as
well as stable coin use cases and just all of this like stuff that's being built around stable
coins and just super excited about like the future of crypto being driven by stable coins.
In terms of what keeps me up at night, it's kind of like the other side of the coin, which is just
like, this is a massive, massive opportunity. Yeah. What I spend most of my time thinking
about is like, how do we build products to actually be able to capture this opportunity?
Because it's like, not everyone's going to be a winner. There is a lot of competition. And then
it's like, I think we do have to be very strategic about what we build and how we go to market.
Yeah. That's probably just like what I spend most of my days and nights thinking about.
Awesome. Well, I'll leave it there. Keddy, and thanks for coming on and really enjoyed
chatting. Hopefully we can do it again soon. Yeah, I appreciate it. This was fun.
Thanks for listening to another episode of On the Brink with Castle Island. To find out
more about Castle Island, visit castleisland.vc. To listen to all of our podcast episodes,
please go to onthebrink-podcast.com or just click on the tab in our website. Thanks for listening.